Twitches Too is a drama, family, fantasy film directed by Stuart Gillard.
Reunited witch twins Camryn and Alex adjust to their new life as supernatural beings while at the same time trying
to maintain a normal existence in this sequel to the magical Disney Channel original movie Twitches.
But they soon find themselves going head to head with the forces
of darkness that threaten to destroy their world.
Luckily, their birth mother, the powerful Miranda, is on hand to help out.
Alex Fielding, played by Tia Mowry.
Camryn Barnes, played by Tamera Mowry-Housley.
Miranda, played by Kristen Wilson.
Thantos, played by Patrick Fabian.
Karsh, played by Pat Kelly.
Ileana, played by Leslie Seiler.
Twitches Too is a 2007 American fantasy drama film
released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It is the sequel to the Disney Channel Original
Movie Twitches, released in 2005.
The film began production in late April 2007 and was released on October 12.
It aired during Disney Channel's Halloween Month.
The Disney Channel Original Series, Wizards of Waverly
Place, premiered following the film's premiere.
The first trailer was released during the premiere of High School Musical 2.
On its premiere night, the movie brought in 6.96 million viewers.
For 15 years, it was the last non-musical Disney Channel Original
Movie sequel to be produced until  Under Wraps 2 (2022).
The film explores themes of witch, sequel, missing parent.
The tone is dark and emotional.